[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'みなみ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Південь"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'りょこうします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Подорожувати"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'すてき' read in word?",
        "answer": "Чудовий"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さん ご うす' read in word?",
        "answer": "Кораловий риф"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'めずらしい' read in word?",
        "answer": "Рідкісний"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ほんとう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Правда"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おきなわ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Окінава"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いろいろ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Різноманітний"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Схід"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'すばらしい' read in word?",
        "answer": "кльовий, класний, красивий"
    }
]
